Sheila.
希拉
- Hi. - Look at you.
-你好  -看看你
- You're lovely. - Thanks.
-你真漂亮  -谢谢
Oh, I'm so nervous.
我好紧张
You're going to be great.
没事的
Hey, kid, you're on in ten.
孩子  再过10分钟就该你了
Oh, thank you, Mr. Porter.
谢谢你  波特先生
What are you looking for?
你在看什么
It's silly. Rob told me he can't make it.
说来挺傻的  罗伯说他不能来了
I just... I keep thinking maybe he'll surprise me.
我  我总觉得他也许会给我个惊喜
Honey, you can't worry about that right now.
宝贝  你现在不能想这个
You've got a show to do.
你马上就要表演了
You're right. Thank you so much for being here.
你说得没错  感谢你能来这里看我表演
Knock 'em dead.
惊艳全场吧
Okay.
好的
* When I was just a little girl *
*我还是小女孩的时候*
* I asked my mother, What will I be? *
*我问我妈妈  我会成为什么*
* Will I be pretty, will I be rich? *
*我会变得漂亮吗  我会变得有钱吗*
* Here's what she said to me *
*她这么对我说*
* Que será, será *
*天意难违*
* Whatever will be, will be *
*该来的总会来*
* The future's not ours to see *
*我们无法预知未来*
* Que será, será *
*天意难违*
* What will be, will be... *
*该来的总会来*